# Nanette Julius

Email: njulius89@gmail.com | Cell: (661) 993-7831 https://linkedin.com/in/nanette-julius/ | https://github.com/njulius89 | www.nanettejulius.com

## **SUMMARY**

Creative problem-solving full stack web developer with the coordinating and interpersonal skills to match. I create user friendly, visually appealing applications that are functional and organized. Strong detail, communication and leadership skills developed through teaching experience.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Materialize, JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive Design, UX/UI Design, React.js, JSON, REST, AJAX, Firebase, Photoshop, WordPress, Chrome Dev Tools, GIT, GitHub, Node.js, Express, React Native, Google Firebase, SQL, Handlebars JS and MongoDB.

#### **EDUCATION**

University of California Los Angeles, Los Angeles , CA *Certificate, Full Stack Web Development* 

2017

Cal State University Los Angeles, Los Angeles, CA B.A. Music Education

2013

#### **APPLICATIONS BUILT**

# Swapr

- A full stack web app for trading goods with other users nearby. Users can search for items within a set distance using google maps API and arrange to meet and trade.
- <a href="https://swapr-app.herokuapp.com/">https://swapr-app.herokuapp.com/</a>

# EventStay

- A frontend web app routing users to hotels near their desired events. Users can choose an event anywhere in the world and find the cheapest, highest rated hotels near it.
- https://njulius89.github.io/EventStay/

#### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

REX IT Inc. – Pasadena, CA

06/2016 to 07/2017

- Junior Web Developer
  - Designed clean, user-friendly, responsive websites/web applications
  - Ensured the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs
  - Developed new user-facing features
  - Helped other engineers with bug fixes and feature development
  - Application testing and improving test coverage

### **EMPLOYMENT**

Gorman Learning Center – Santa Clarita, CA Performing Arts Program Director/ Music Teacher

08/2015 to 06/2017

Heritage Christian School - Granada Hills, CA

07/2014 to 06/2015

# Elementary Music Teacher/ Chapel Coordinator

Real Life Church - Santa Clarita, CA Music Department Coordinator 01/2012 to 6/2014